{
    "id": "28449d7806f34fc3883a5e7f8edd538f",
    "title": "Each And Every",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I call my mother every ..................",
            "description": "We use a singular noun after every.",
            "answers": [
                "week",
                "weeks",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There were shops on ............................ side of the street.",
            "description": "Each is used to speak of two or more people or things. Every is used to speak of more than two people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "each",
                "every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The two brothers love ............................ other.",
            "description": "The correct expression is each other.",
            "answers": [
                "each",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Everyone ............................. arrived.",
            "description": "We use a singular verb after every and everyone.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She gave them ............................ a kiss on the forehead.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "each",
                "every",
                "everyone"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I looked in ............................... cupboard but I could not find the photo.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "each",
                "every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I spoke to .............................. of the parents there.",
            "description": "We cannot use every before of.",
            "answers": [
                "each",
                "Every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to meet ................................ of them.",
            "description": "We can use each or every one before of.",
            "answers": [
                "each",
                "every one",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "................................ was delighted to hear the news.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Everybody",
                "Each",
                "Every body"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I enjoyed ............................. minute of the holiday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "every",
                "everyone",
                "every one"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have read .................................. of the books on that shelf.",
            "description": "We cannot use every before of.",
            "answers": [
                "each",
                "every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I know ................................... of them.",
            "description": "We can use each or every one before of.",
            "answers": [
                "each",
                "every one",
                "everyone"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}